

KELLEN CERIANI

Dana Point, CA

(949)910-6430

kellenceriani@u.boisestate.edu

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SOSCA Drumline/Marching Band-

3 school years in both Marching Band and Drumline throughout high school career in which experienced countless competitions and events-Medals, Plaques, & Trophies attained (2017- 2019)

BTMB- Currently part of the Blue Thunder Marching Band for Boise State University.

American Red Cross- Completed American red Cross First Aid Instructional at Junior Guards program and knowledgeable of CPR (2016)

Assistant coaching- for baseball at the community center by Ralph's and soccer at Laguna Niguel (2015)

Junior lifeguards- helped out at strands beach with the OC Jr. Lifeguard program after completing 4 years of Junior Lifeguard Camp at Strands Beach (2012-2016)

EDUCATION

GIMM (Games Interactive Media Mobile), 2024

Boise State University - Boise State

EXPERIENCE

2D Artist/Animator, 12/2021 to 03/2022

GIMM - Boise, ID

- Designed inspiring concept art while maintaining accurate scale and architectural standards.
- Collaborated with creative design team to complete projects on tight deadlines.
- Developed strong working knowledge of games design to enable early identification of potential issues.
- Successfully resolved range of complex artistic development issues for both artists and team members.
- Used Unity, Adobe Animate, Adobe XD, and more to design graphics for signage, packaging and digital promotions.
- Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems.

Line Cook, 05/2020 to 08/2020

Cafe Rio - San Clemente, CA

- Followed strict health and safety guidelines in kitchen.
- Coordinated work of kitchen helpers keeping spaces clean, stocked and tidy.
- Wiped down surfaces, cleaned cookware and sanitized utensils to meet health and safety standards.

Busser, 02/2017 to 05/2019

Cannons Seafood & Grill - Dana Point, CA

- Prepared dishes for up to 60 guests at catering events or during high-volume shifts.
- Cleaned and inspected food preparation areas against safe and sanitary food-handling criteria.
- Cross-trained in table service to support FOH team and maintain consistent staff availability.

SKILLS

- Adobe CC Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Animate, Adobe XD, etc.
- Rotoscoping, Tracing, Animating (2D drawing/design)
- Microsoft Visual Studio C# programming experience
- Audio production and sound design
- Background in music (Marching Band, Drumming, piano, etc.)
- Collaborative working, Leadership, and Time management
- Customer Service, Written/Verbal Communication Skills (COMM101, GIMM, etc.)
- Critical, Creative, & Conceptual Thinking
- Research Capabilities & Proposal Development
- Familiar with HTML & CSS, Microsoft & Google Suites